Translated by Releska
The sky of the starry sky
is so beautiful
I'm going to be a happy day
I'm going to go to the next floor
I'll stay with you in the middle of the night
Of course I'll always be with you
Just a bit more, a bit more
I'll just be with you in the middle of the night
If you don't have a heart like that
The time when the wind blows
The sound of the wind blows
You and me, you and me
If you love me, if you love me
I won't be able to hold you in my arms
If I become a part of a real man, I can become a very human being
We were a world where we lost our early lives
I don't know where we are now
Will we be able to return in the world where we are now?
It's hard to predict
There may be a better time between adults and children
But I would have liked to get out of this world
Muka Muka's Komori-Uta!
Baby!
Come on!
I'll find someone to help you!
Muka Muka, you can't find Senta, right?
If Senta goes to the other side, I'll get her.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm doing okay.
Are you doing okay?
We're in trouble, too.
You're doing okay.
I'll find you.
What?
Oh, you're a monster.
You're a monster!
I can't let you go.
I'm not going to let you go.
I'll make you happy.
What?
If you want to believe, you can go to the other side.
I'll make you happy.
Am I good?
Muka Muka will believe you.
I'll make you happy.
I'll find you.
Muka Muka!
I love you!
It's so hot.
What?
It's so hot that I can't eat it.
I don't think I can eat it.
I'm waiting for the food.
I have a lot of delicious food in my body.
Muka Muka!
Muka Muka has a lot of good food in her body.
Is it yummy?
That's right, right?
Mubeee!
Really?
Yes.
It's the first time I've had such a delicious soup!
I've never had such a delicious soup!
I didn't know that!
It's just now!
I can't find anything that I don't like to eat.
Do you like the blue one?
That's right. I like the blue one that I don't like to eat.
The blue one!
Hey, Uso-chan, do you like it?
We are also in a hurry!
I'm going to...
Take this.
It's a little...
I'm going to eat too!
It's a little bit difficult, but...
Well, that one, right?
What about that one?
Well, that one.
It's a little bit...
Toku, you're lying!
Don't worry, I'm fine now. Let's go.
Is that so?
Hey, you're not eating alone, are you?
That's right.
Hey!
What is it? Your mother is suffering.
I'm tired too.
I want you to listen to Toku and Kishi.
Toku and Kishi!
You're not eating alone, are you?
I'm tired.
Are you okay, Toku?
No!
It's okay if you're okay.
I'm fine if you're hungry.
Yes.
Hurry up.
I'm eating first, so I'll come back soon.
Let's go.
Toku! Toku!
Toku, don't do this to me!
You're right!
Who's that?
That's why we're...
Where did you go, Uluru?
Uluru?
What's wrong?
You're being attacked again.
Everyone's back.
Maybe.
If that's the case, I'm not hungry anymore.
Ah...
I see.
I'm not hungry.
I'll eat you.
I'll cook for you.
Ah, so I'll come back soon.
Oh, you can't stopisoft.
It's too late.
Yeah, I don't think I'll be able to eat because it's too late.
That's right. I'll be able to eat until I get home.
La La La para la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la…
When I go out, I always stay here.
I'll eat it tomorrow.
I'll sleep in the morning.
I'll sleep in the night.
Look, Miro.
I think you should come back when you're ready to eat.
Did you have a long journey?
I'll eat a lot of meat.
Look, look at that.
Dad!
We're going to eat a lot of meat.
Oh, that's right.
Oh, I can't go.
Basmatt!
Oh, it's raining.
It's so cold.
It looks cute.
If you put it like this, it'll get cold.
Is it okay to be still small?
It's cold.
Oh, it's cold.
Wow!
where is it?
wow
wow why is it white?
oh it's on the back!
oh, did i return it?
where did you go?
that is too bad.
maybe it's a bit cold?
I'm hungry!
I don't want to eat it.
Why?
I'm hungry!
What's going on?
It's delicious!
I'll eat it later!
What are you doing, Uiba?
Hurry up!
Where are you going in the morning?
Don't be mad at me.
Come on, come on.
That's right. I didn't see you before.
I saw you yesterday.
You were the same as my friend.
Come on, come on.
You look like a friend?
Cute.
What?
You're different from me.
You're cute.
You're different.
You don't have mom?
Cute.
No.
You're so good.
You're eating a lot.
What?
You're so cute.
What's your father's name?
I don't know.
But I'm so cute.
Maybe you're a little bit shy.
But you're so surprised.
You're already a little bit shy.
Stop it, you're so cute.
You're so stupid.
You're so cute.
Sorry, Daichi.
What's wrong? You're so cute.
That's...
It's cold.
No.
You're too lazy.
You look like you're taking care of Aka-chan.
But it's like I'm doing some research.
I'm taking care of Aka-chan too.
I think you're taking care of a little bit.
W, W, W...
I want to hide from you at night because I can't see you.
You must keep your close eyes on me, Akka-chan.
Okay, okay!
Shall I be like this for a moment?
Huh?!
H, H, H...
...I was also thinking it was really Mom doing things stupid.
Really?
What?
I mean, I was like,
I'm sorry!
I thought you were going to be mad at me!
I'm not mad!
I was just kidding!
I'm not mad at you!
I'm just kidding!
What?
It's not a big deal!
I'm not mad at you!
Look!
You're not mad at me!
I'm not mad at you!
No!
If you don't,
you're not mad at me!
I'm not mad at you!
No!
What if I was mad at you?
If I was mad at you,
I would have been mad at you!
I'm not mad at you!
You're not mad at me!
He's not mad at me.
He's not mad at you!
I'm not mad at you.
What do you mean you're pretending?
When he'srockconfed,
he's easy to put himself in rock seeking!
Knock through.
We're strong to Life!
Explain it to Mother, Miracle!
I'm not mad at you.
I'm not mad at you!
I'm not there anymore
I'm in the deep forest
where I'm looking for the future
Well, I'll have to go now.
I'll have to go now.
What's the matter with you?
Don't worry, I'll be there.
No!
What are you laughing at?
What's the matter?
I thought you were going to teach me something.
What?
What's the matter?
So, I'm going to go to the water pool.
I'm going to be a real cat.
I'm not going to teach you something.
Is this the same thing as the red one?
It's like a red one.
I'm not going to teach you something.
What are you doing?
Look at that.
It's rare.
It's not rare.
It's rare?
Yeah, it's rare.
It's rare that the red one has a child in a water pool.
There are many water pool.
What?
You and Papa are on the way.
Yes.
The next month, I'll get to the water pool.
If you say that, it's not a cat.
Yeah.
Do you know Muka Muka?
Yeah, I don't even know what to say.
Life is a lie.
It's the beginning of Muka Muka.
Muka Muka is a little too difficult.
Kaguya Hime has to go back to the moon.
Muka Muka said something.
She went to find Muka Muka.
Huh?
I'm here!
I want to go back.
Muka Muka said something.
No!
Goodbye!
That's right, that's right, that's always there
When I hear the voice, I hear it here
It's strange, it's strange, it's strange
I'm the only one who can't say anything
Ehhh?
It's so difficult.
I can't get out of the bush!
The moment you leave us, it gets alienated!
In the end, the stone breaks and becomes a pile of mud!
It's so difficult to get out of it!
This is a destiny!
And what about you, my kid?
Stay tuned for the next episode!
Bye!